<dream name="JUNGLEDREAM">
	<card name="root">
		<show>
			<p>You wake up. You're in a jungle. You hear a tiger roar. {sound} It sounds really close! What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Run!</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Run!"/>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Give Up and Die!</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Give Up and Die!"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Run!">
		<show>
			<p>You run from the tiger as fast as your hobbit legs can carry you. You hear rustling and growling {sound} as the tiger hears you and gives chase. You find a small yurt, just in the knick of time, run in, and slam the straw door, thinking &quot;That probably won't hold...&quot; What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Jump in the fireplace!</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Jump in the fireplace!"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Jump in the fireplace!">
		<show>
			<p>With a running start, you dive headfirst into the fireplace, {sound} {wilhelm scream?} where you are instantly killed. If you die in dreams, you die in real life. So you are now dead. But you are also a ghost in real life. So you were already dead. Realizing this, you float out of your lifeless body and are now a ghost in this dream. You wake up. You are dead. You float up out of your lifeless body and see the tiger burst into the door so hard it splats right into an iron headboard and onto the bed below, out cold. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess the tiger</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You possess the sleeping tiger. You notice the alarm clock is set to 2 minutes.</p>
				<exit dream="GOLDFISHBOWLDREAM"/>
			</reveal>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Give Up and Die!">
		<show>
			<p>You give up, you shout out to the tiger, &quot;Here kitty kitty, come eat me!&quot; The tiger obliges. {sound} {death} You are dead. If you die in dreams, you die in real life. So you are now dead. But you are also a ghost in real life. So you were already dead. Realizing this, you float out of your lifeless body and are now a ghost in this dream. The clock is ticking... What do you want to do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Fly!</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Fly!"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Fly!">
		<show>
			<p>You fly high into the clouds and see the entire world is smoldering ashes and badlands except for that beautiful little jungle. You keep flying for a very long time. You begin to miss that precious little emerald miles below you. Suddenly you fly right through some kind of floating fortress. By the grimy walls, faint moans and clanging of metal, you are cleary in some kind of dungeon.</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Left</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go Left"/>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Right</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go Right#"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go Left">
		<show>
			<p>You go left. There is a massive door blocking your way. You use your ghostly powers of deduction to deduce - after failing to charge right through the door and succeeding in bumping your ghostly little noggin - that the door is in fact magical and requires a magical key to unlock. You're pretty sure you hear some snoring on the other side of this door. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
			<p>NEW QUEST: Find the Magical Key to unlock the Magical Bedroom Door in the Flying Fortress in the Jungle Dream.</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Back the other way</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go Back the other way"/>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Wait for the love of your life to show up</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>Any time now...</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go Back the other way">
		<show>
			<p>You go back. Now what?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Right</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go Right"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go Right">
		<show>
			<p>You go right. And you were right! Here's an old granny sleeping on a bed. At first you're not sure if she's alive, but sure enough, you can hear the faintest snore as you get close. There is an alarm clock on the bed set for 8:00 AM; thanks to magical ghost powers you know it's about 7:58 AM right now. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess the dreamer</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You possess the granny. You take the alarm clock and shove it into your ghost body as you dive into your next dream.</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go Right#">
		<show>
			<p>You go right. And you were right! Here's an old granny sleeping on a bed. At first you're not sure if she's alive, but sure enough you can hear the faintest snore as you get close. There is an alarm clock on the bed set for 8:00 AM; thanks to magical ghost powers you know it's about 7:58 AM right now. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess the dreamer</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You possess the granny. You take the alarm clock and shove it into your ghost body as you dive into your next dream.</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go back</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go back"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go back">
		<show>
			<p>You go back.</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Left</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You go left. There is a massive door blocking your way. You use your ghostly powers of deduction to deduce - after failing to charge right through the door and succeeding in bumping your ghostly little noggin - that the door is in fact magical and requires a magical key to unlock. You're pretty sure you hear some snoring on the other side of this door. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
				<p>NEW QUEST: Find the Magical Key to unlock the Magical Bedroom Door in the Flying Fortress in the Jungle Dream.</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Go Right</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Go Right##"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Go Right##">
		<show>
			<p>You go right. And you were right! Here's an old granny sleeping on a bed. At first you're not sure if she's alive, but sure enough, you can hear the faintest snore as you get close. There is an alarm clock on the bed set for 8:00 AM; thanks to magical ghost powers you know it's about 7:58 AM right now. Time is ticking. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess the dreamer</p>
			</label>
			<reveal/>
		</button>
	</card>
</dream>
