<dream name="SPACEDREAM">
	<card name="root">
		<show>
			<p>You wake up. You're a space man! No wait, you're in space, ma'am! Like floating out in space, watching the space station get smaller and smaller in front of you. What do you do?</p>
			<audio src="/Sound/Space-theme.mp3"/>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Activate Propulsion Socks</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You activate your propulsion socks. They don't work. With sheer willpower you launch yourself at the space station anyway and eventually make it. Unfortunately, there is a robot inside who will not open the pod bay doors to let you in. After a candid radio chat, you determine all he wants from life is a red hat. {ITEM NEEDED}{RED HAT}</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Merge with the Omnipresent Void of the Infinite Cosmos</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Merge with the Omnipresent Void of the Infinite Cosmos"/>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Take off your Helmet and accept your fate</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Take off your Helmet and accept your fate"/>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<audio src="Happy-theme"/>
			</label>
			<go card="&lt;audio src=&quot;Happy-theme&quot;/&gt;"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Merge with the Omnipresent Void of the Infinite Cosmos">
		<show>
			<p>You merge with the Omnipresent Void of the Infinite Cosmos. You are one with OVIC. OVIC is one with you. Cheat codes enabled... You learn your lover is in hypersleep in the space station. Then with a great sneeze OVIC expels you, a little astronaut-shaped booger flying through space. You fly so fast that you open a wormhole and find yourself suddenly in a white room with a small white bed where a large white rat is sleeping. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Kill the rat</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You pull out a raygun and shoot the rat. Well you killed them. congRATS! Now you're trapped in a white room with nothing else to do. Too bad you can't just like wake up out of this drea-- oh wait...</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Kill yourself</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Kill yourself"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Kill yourself">
		<show>
			<p>You pull out a raygun and shoot yourself. You wake up. You are dead. You lift up out of your lifeless body and see the rat still asleep on the bed. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Celebrate</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You dance a little ghostly jig.</p>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Haunt Their Dreams!!!</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You possess the rat. Oops! You almost forgot; you reach out, take the alarm clock, and shove it in your ghostly body.</p>
				<exit dream="GOLDFISHBOWLDREAM"/>
			</reveal>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Take off your Helmet and accept your fate">
		<show>
			<p><i>Pchhhh  sssssss* The internal pressure releases as you take off your helmet. The total lack of external pressure results in the immediate and total explosion of your face. You are dead. You float out of your lifeless body *cuh cuh gluh</i> You are a ghost. Ghosts cannot breathe in space. You suffocate. You are dead again. You are a ghost of your former ghostly self. Fortunately ghosts of ghosts can breathe in space. #DreamLogic Yep. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess your ghost corpse</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Possess your ghost corpse"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Possess your ghost corpse">
		<show>
			<p>You possess your ghost corpse. What do you do?</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Possess what's left of your original body</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Possess what's left of your original body"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Possess what's left of your original body">
		<show>
			<p>You possess your remains... Ewww... They should call you Gross Ghost, because that's just ... ewww... What do you - you know what I can't even write this out it's so gross. I'm gonna go take a shower and wipe all this grossness off of me.</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Take control of the narrative</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>I have taken control of the narrative. It's mine. All mine!!!! AH HAHAHAH AHHAHAHHAHHAHAHHAHHAHAHH AHAHHA AHHAHAHAHHAHHAHAHAHHAHHAHAHAHAHHAHHAHAHHA. Wow! A bed appears floating in space, and check that out: a wandering erg-lob is sleeping peacefully on the bed. I possess the erg-lob... and lose control of the narrative - woooh that was close. Good thing I take really fast showers. So the alarm clock next to the erg-lob is set to @#&amp;%<i>&amp;HFDI!</i>U(#$):}{+-7, which means you should have approximately three minutes before She wakes up. Good luck, you fourth-wall-breaker you. Oops! You almost forgot; you reach out, take the alarm clock, and shove it in your ghostly body.</p>
				<exit dream="EPICBATTLEDREAM"/>
			</reveal>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="&lt;audio src=&quot;Happy-theme&quot;/&gt;">
		<show/>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>HAUNT THEIR DREAMS!!!</p>
			</label>
			<reveal>
				<p>You possess the giant. Oops! You almost forgot; you reach out, take the alarm clock, and shove it in your ghostly body.</p>
				<exit dream="GARDENGNOMEDREAM"/>
			</reveal>
		</button>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>Do something else!</p>
			</label>
			<go card="Do something else!"/>
		</button>
	</card>
	<card name="Do something else!">
		<show>
			<p>Really? You really just want to do &quot;something else&quot;? You don't even know what &quot;something else&quot; is. Just haunt their dreams!</p>
		</show>
		<button>
			<label>
				<p>I still want to do something else...</p>
			</label>
			<reveal/>
		</button>
	</card>
</dream>
